Design and evaluation of a prototype of augmented reality applied to
medical devices
-"Even though use of medical devices is extremely beneficial for patient care, potential problems associated with their use may produce
severe, negative consequences, compromising patient safety."

-"medical device manufacturers
are obliged by Spanish legislation for each device to include “the necessary information to use it completely safely and properly, considering potential users’ training and knowledge, and to identify the
manufacturer”"

-"Participation from the research team, as future users, led to
a participatory design involving users in the design of the device [22].
"

General Requirements for Industrial Augmented Reality Applications
-" Although Augmented Reality applications have been used
successfully in medical or military contexts for many years, industrial applications are often perceived as isolated solutions that are only applicable
in a defined and static work environment."

-" Although the integration of individual workpieces is a strongly desired feature, it requires considerable development effort, which leads to additional
costs and cannot be performed instantly."

Pottential applications for virtual and augmented reality technologies in sensory science
-". Increasingly, sensory data techniques are moving towards
more dynamic aspects of sensory perception, taking account of the various stages of user-product interactions.
Recent technological advancements in virtual reality and augmented reality have unlocked the potential for new
immersive and interactive systems which could be applied as powerful tools for capturing and deciphering the
complexities of human sensory perception."

-"Augmented reality is a relatively newer form of human-computer interaction which superimposes computer-generated information into a
person's view of the real world, creating an illusion where both virtual and real objects coexist in the same space (Ong & Nee, 2004)"

-"Therefore, AR can be differentiated from VR, given that the former overlays
digital information in a real environment, rather than completely replacing it. In addition to combining real and virtual information, a true
AR system should run interactively in real time, and seamlessly align
natural world and virtual objects with each other (Azuma et al., 2001;
Kipper & Rampolia, 2013)."

-"The earliest technological development in AR can be traced back to Ivan Sutherland's work on the Swords of Damocles HMD."

-"recreating a physical
immersive environment could improve the ecological validity of research, it requires a relatively large amount of space and can be a rather
expensive and time-consuming task."

-"However, regardless of the approach, it must be kept
in mind that research on the contextual effects VR/AR environments is
in its infancy, and further research is necessary to facilitate their confident application in improving the reliability of consumer sensory
evaluations."

-"therefore the accuracy of
the data is dependent on the individual's ability to articulate their hedonic and emotional perceptions to food stimuli."

-"VR and AR can also enable the interactive visualisation of complex food ingredient structures and their interplay with dynamic sensory data, enhancing our understanding of oral food processing, potentially leading to new manufacturing practices, food products and
customer experiences"

Towards augmented reality manuals for industry 4.0: A methodology.
-"These innovations in ICT (Information and Communication Technologies) and computer sciences a?ect also industrial manufacturing. Started in Germany, this trend is called the 4th Industrial Revolution, in shorthand, Industry 4.0 [1]."

Potentials of Augmented Reality in Training 
-"The debate surrounding about changing processes by using new technologies, this also implies a change in the way people work."
-"This raises the question of how far digital supporting systems, in particular AR technologies, not only improve the process itself, but can also be used as an innovative medium for practice-oriented learning."

Augmented reality in support of Industry 4.0—Implementation challenges and success factors
-"AR is an important technology for the Industry4.0 approach[2]. As those approaches promote a human-centric industrial environment, AR is one approach to augment the worker[12]."
-"AR is a complex technology.Thiscomplexity arises on the one hand from the technology itself. The system has to be integrated into the current IT infrastructure"
-"The availability of innovative computer graphics interfaces, like Augmented and Virtual Reality, can change signiﬁcantly the way technicalinformationispresentedtotheuser"
-"In the industrial ﬁeld, AR or VR contents have been proposed as a support for maintenance [22,37], for assembly simulation [38–41] sometimes including tactile communication and also to improve information delivery and 
perception in manufacturing systems [42]. Furthermore VR has also been proposed as a tool to support industrial processes, for example to improve processes control [43], 
to analyze and improve ergonomics [44] or to study and analyze human-robot interaction [45]."
-" In AR manuals it is important to provide only the needed information without useless details because they imply the use of text that occludes the real scene and is diﬃcult to relate unambiguously with the rest of instruction provided with visual elements."

Design Considerations for combining Augmented Reality with intelligent tutors.
-"A simple Google scholar search on “Intelligent Tutoring Systems” returns more than 57,000 results, whereas search on “Intelligent Tutoring Systems and Augmented Reality” returns a mere 57 results."
-"AR is a subset of “mixed reality”, the blending of physical and virtual worlds (Fig. 2) [21]."

Design Considerations for combining Augmented Reality with intelligent tutors.
-"The Virtual and Augmented Reality Design System (VADS) is a training system that uses both AR and VR to help mechanical engineers develop their own problem solving and mechanical ability using a personalised learning approach."

Mobile Augmented Reality: the potential for education
-"Due to the rising popularity of mobile devices globally, the widespread use of AR on mobile devices such as smartphones and tablets has become a growing phenomenon. "
-"The transformation of teaching and learning caused by technology has certainly provides an exciting opportunities to design learning environment that are realistic, authentic, engaging and extremely fun."

Perspectives on how to evaluate augmented reality technology tools for education: a systematic review
-".The coexistence of virtual and real environments allows learners to experience phenomena that otherwise would be impossible in the real world.This allows learners to visualize complex spatial relationships and abstract concepts and,therefore,develop important abilities that cannot be evolved in other technology learning environments[78]."

Supporting remote maintenance in industry 4.0 through augmented reality 
-" the maintenance expert should be able to see why and where the failure occurred, to understand how to perform the maintenance activity"

A MOBILE APPLICATION OF AUGMENTED REALITY FOR AEROSPACE MAINTENANCE TRAINING
-""

Retargeting Technical Documentation to Augmented Reality
-""

Linking person-job fit to job stress: The mediating effect of perceived person-organization fit 
-"Job performance of employees and stress at work are very common problems in today’s business world. Many people change their jobs due to high job stress which affects their personal well-being. "
- "Whilst employees can be reasonably expected to adjust to changes in jobs over time, poor job or employee job fit can result in increased stress and inefficiency in organizations"
- ". The better a person “fits” with his job, the less adjusting and performance problems occur"
- " the employee’s suitability is not compatible with the job, this stress is elevated and compounded causing psychological and physiological damage and rendering the employee less capable of performing the expected tasks."
- "  Person-Job fit is described as a match between the personal knowledge, skills and abilities of the employee and requırements of the job or, the needs / desires of a person which the job is able to supply (Brkich, Jeffs & Careless, 2002). Person Job fit has two dimensions: “Person-Job Fit and Person-Job Unfit” (Brkich et al. 2002). "
- "Work stress is always a serious issue in the modern business world. "
- " When humans feel a loss of control this causes physiological changes which can exacerbate feelings of stress. "

A Study on the Job Training Effectiveness: Empirical Evidence of Iran
- "Any organization that wants to succeed, and to continue to succeed, has to maintain workforce consisting of people who are willing to learn and develop continuously"
-". Training and developing human capital is tremendously important in the effective management and maintenance of a skilled workforce. Training is one of the ways of improving organization’s effectiveness. In order to implement right training methods, organization should be aware of the training methods and their effectiveness"
- "The verb “to train” is derived from the old French word trainer, meaning “to drag”. Hence such English definitions may be found as; to draw along; to allure; to cause; to grow in the desired manner; to prepare for performance by instruction, practice exercise, "
- " Procedural knowledge is the person’s understandings about how and when to apply the facts hat has been learned.
- "Skill is the capacities needed to perform a set of tasks that are developed as a result of training and experience"
- " Training is a situational process that is why no single method is right for every situation. "
-"Training methods could be classified as cognitive and behavioral approaches. Cognitive methods provide verbal or written information, demonstrate relationships among concepts, or provide the rules for how to do something. These types of methods can also be called as off the job training methods. On the other hand, behavioral methods allow trainee to practice behavior in real or simulated fashion. "
- "Mental models are mental or internal conceptual representations of the software package (Foley, 1980; Bentley, 1994). They aid users in making inferences about the system, reasoning about it, and guiding actions."
- "Conceptual models can be classified as the analogical and abstract models. Analogical representations present the system to be learned in terms of another system."


A Study on the Impact of on the job training Courses on the Staff Performance (A Case Study) 
 - "In recent years many organizations have been busy implementing new or improved performance management systems. Recent research shows that the regular use of these systems leads to better organizational results. (Ahn, 2001; Ittner et al. 2003; Lawson et al. 2005; Said et al., 2003; Sandt et al, 2001)."
- "The major impact of training on the organizations can be summed up as follows: x Improving the quantity and quality of organizations output. x Increasing the chance of organizational success. x Safeguards the organizational stability. x Decreasing the risk of processes. x Decreasing organizational costs and expenses x Improving the management of the organization. x Establishing the organization as national and international entities. "
- "Training, which aims at empowerment, development, and qualifying employees through knowledge and skills, referrers to end-oriented,  organized, logical, on-going planned attempts to bring about the desired, change in the knowledge, skills, capability and attitude employees. "

User Profiling for University Recommender System using Automatic Information Retrieval 
- "User Profiling is the process of Extracting, Integrating and Identifying the keyword based information to generate a structured Profile and then visualizing the knowledge out of these findings."
- "personalization is one of the major concepts used for accessing the user relevant information, which can be used to solve the difficult problems"
- "when humans come across making choice they find it difficult to obtain the most suitable information that is hidden in the deluge of information."
- "User profiling is typically either knowledge-based (already known/factual) or behavior-based"
- "User profile generation is done when we get users complete information while he registers into our system. We have identified different user attributes for profiling him into our system"

User Profiling Trends, Techniques and Applications
- "With
personalization these systems can generate user specific recommendations accurately and
efficiently. User profiling helps personalization, where information retrieval is done to
personalize a scenario which maintains a separate user profile for individual user."
- "There are many users which a recommender system needs to
deal with, and each user has their own preference requirements."
- "So user profiling helps recommender system to know user requirements and behave in accordance of them."
- "User Profiling can be defined as the process of identifying the data about a user interest domain"
- "This paper surveys user profiling in three main contexts. First the trends in the user profiling are identified to show how the user profiling evolved from the recommender systems, then we go on discussing the techniques used for profiling the users, finally the paper gives some case studies on how User Profiling has been applied in various domains."
- "User profiling in general started with the just information retrieval and collection of the user’s information"


A Survey of Augmented Reality Navigation
-For example, showing navigation
markers on the windshield of the car or augmenting the video
camera output of a smartphone with the navigation path, etc.
-popular navigation systems that are on the market are smartphone applications or standalone systems that
make use of a mapping service and satellite localization.
conventional navigation systems show navigation
information in an abstracted form by typically showing arrows pointing towards the intended direction or by providing
a "bird’s eye view" of the map and the intended path.
-1. Acquire the real world view from the user’s perspective.
2. Acquire the location information for tracking the user.
This information is typically the GPS coordinates.
3. Generate the virtual world information based on the real
world view and the location information.
4. Register the virtual information generated with the real
world view and display the information to the user,
thereby creating an augmented rea
-tion.
-A lot of smartphone navigation applications like HUDWAY [3] and Sygic [5] HUD try to reflect the smartphone
screen onto the windshield.
-Another challenge of augmented reality is registration.
Registration is the process of correctly aligning the virtual
information with the real world in order to preserve the illusion of coexistence. 
-"Navigation information can be presented to the user in many ways. A few examples include, pointing arrows towards the intended direction or by painting the road with transclucent colour "
-"Thus, the system should provide navigation cues and assistance using audio."
-" But it is also important to note that while context speciﬁc information is useful, it should not block the the user’s view or clutter the display with excessive information."
-"The system does not track the user’s location continuously, instead it uses information points(way-points)printedontheﬂoortodetectthelocation of user."
-"the user needs to updatehis/herlocationbyscanninganotherway-pointonthe way."

The Vuforia SDK and Unity3D Game Engine – Evaluating Performance on Android Devices
-" most popular SDK for developing AR-applications on a wide selection of devices. "
- "These include tracking, image recognition, object recognition, text recognition, video playback."
- " Natural features in images are usually sharp details such as high contrast corners or the tips of a triangle "
	-"Each section is shifted in several directions and the change in image intensity (RGB value) is measured. "
	-"the feature tracking algorithm can determine what is a feature and map the positions of these features in the image."
Whenthetargetisdetectedbytheapplication,thefeaturesarematched against pre-deﬁned feature patterns and the pose of that target is estimated [26]. Pose is a common term used in the area of computer vision. It is the combination of position and orientation, often in relation to a 2D coordinate system. In Vuforia’s case, the coordinate system is made up of the pattern created by the natural feature tracking.
- "A target is a pattern of natural features pre-deﬁned by the developer or user."
-"Vuforia offer developers a web service to create targets from 2D images, cuboids, cylinders and 3D objects "
-"Extended tracking is a feature that allows Vuforia to track targets using natural features surrounding it."
-"good targets contain a higher number of features arranged as uniquely as possible. "
-"Images of round shapes without sharp edges would also make bad targets, "
-" In reality the “scanning plane” or Object Recognition Target is an image target that, when detected, provides the scanner with the XYZ-coordinates of the detected features on the 3Dobject."
-"Vuforia allows for 20 object targets in the one device database "
- "InterestPointDetection. Interest point detection works by having a set of template images, capturing the object appearance and pre-deﬁned feature patterns. As features are detected by the tracker, they are compared to the features – interest points – of the template images and the orientation can be calculated"
- "The text recognition component of Vuforia is made possible by something called the“text recognition engine” [23] and there are no available speciﬁcations of this “engine”. What is known, however, is that text recognition on mobile devices is enabled by something called Optical Character Recognition, thus a short description of this will be provided. "
- " . The image then undergoes some form of segmentation where the text is being differentiated fromo the graphical elements in the image. "

Vuforia Developer Portal
-"Added a new feature to train Model Target Databases containing multiple views and/or multiple objects with automatic recognition. Refer to the documentation Trained Model Target Datasets on how to use these databases."